So let's get started with in a go.
所以让我们开始吧。
One of the most common issues that I've seen with English learners is mixing up in and go with after
我在英语学习者身上看到的最常见的问题之一是混入和追随
AND before and later we can't get these mixed up.
而且之前和之后我们不能把这些搞混。
We use in and go in one type of situation and the others in a different one.
我们在一种情况下使用和进入，而其他情况则在不同的情况下使用。
So let's just be very clear about how we use it and to go.
所以让我们非常清楚我们如何使用它和去。
So this is our timeline.
所以这是我们的时间表。
It's called Is Our timeline and this is now the present this moment if we're talking about something
它被称为是我们的时间线，如果我们在谈论某事，这就是现在这个时刻
from now then we should use in if it's in the future and to go for the past.
从现在开始，如果它是在未来，我们应该使用 in 并为过去使用。
So this way the future we'll use in again.
所以这种方式将来我们会再次使用。
This is from now from now we can't say for example we can't say after 10 minutes.
这是从现在起我们不能说，例如我们不能在 10 分钟后说。
And that means from now 10 minutes we need to say in 10 minutes in the past we use a go from now.
这意味着从现在开始 10 分钟，我们需要说在过去 10 分钟内我们使用从现在开始。
We can't say 10 minutes before.
我们不能说 10 分钟前。
Now we can't say that we have to say 10 minutes ago.
现在我们不能说我们必须说 10 分钟前。
It doesn't matter how much time it is it can be 100 years 50 years a week a month 10 months a minute
不管有多少时间 可以是 100 年 50 年 每周 1 个月 10 个月 一分钟
a second doesn't matter from now.
从现在开始，一秒钟都没有关系。
OK.
好的。
Some examples some examples.
一些例子一些例子。
The plane plane will land in 10.
这架飞机将于10点降落。
I'm just going to write the abbreviation M I N S 10 minutes.
我只是要写缩写 M I N S 10 分钟。
OK.
好的。
My plane my plane left ten minutes ago.
我的飞机我的飞机十分钟前离开了。
OK so the first one the plane will leave in 10 minutes or will land and 10 minutes sorry the plane will
好的，所以第一个飞机将在 10 分钟内起飞或降落，然后 10 分钟抱歉，飞机将
land in 10 minutes means I'm sitting here waiting.
Land in 10 minutes 意味着我正坐在这里等待。
The plane is going to in the future from now 10 minutes my plane left 10 minutes ago that means I'm
这架飞机将从现在开始 10 分钟 未来 10 分钟 我的飞机在 10 分钟前离开 这意味着我
late.
晚的。
I ran to the airport and it didn't make it.
我跑到机场，它没有成功。
I'm late for my plane I'm late for my flight because it left 10 minutes ago.
我的飞机迟到了 我的航班迟到了，因为它在 10 分钟前起飞。
OK.
好的。
Again that's from now.
从现在开始。
That's from now in 15 years.
那是15年后的现在。
I hope to be living in Sweden.
我希望住在瑞典。
OK Sweden.
好的瑞典。
I don't know why Sweden.
不知道为什么是瑞典。
Who knows.
谁知道。
In 15 years I hope to be living in Sweden.
15 年后，我希望住在瑞典。
OK.
好的。
So that's in the future maybe this is 2015 and this is 2030 from now if it's 2015.
所以那是在未来，也许这是 2015 年，如果是 2015 年，那么现在是 2030 年。
Actually it's not from now 30 15 years to 2030.
实际上不是从现在 30 到 15 年到 2030 年。
It's very important that it's from now.
从现在开始非常重要。
Doesn't matter how much time it is.
不管是多少时间。
Doesn't matter.
没关系。
OK.
好的。
I was living in Ohio four years ago.
四年前我住在俄亥俄州。
So from now if we go back one two three four years.
所以从现在开始，如果我们回到一二三四年。
Where was I Ohio.
我在哪里俄亥俄州。
I was living there.
我住在那里。
OK actually that's also not true.
好的，实际上这也不是真的。
Just examples.
只是例子。
I hope that's clear in the future from now.
我希望从现在开始，这在未来很清楚。
Go to the past.
回到过去。
From now.
现在起。